A Guide to the Papers of Rita Mae Brown 1929-2001
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Literary Papers and Manuscripts
  - Book Manuscripts and Typescripts by Rita Mae Brown
    - Pawings Through the Past First Draft with First Corrections [ca. 1998 Jan], 285 pages; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Pawing Through the Past First Draft Clean Copy 1998 Jan 14, 285 pages; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Pawing Through the Past Second Draft 1998 Jun, 285 pages; 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Pawing Through the Past Page Proofs, Second Pass 2000 Jan 6, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Pawing Through the Past--Correspondence and Reviews 2000 (Box 47)
    - Pawing Through the Past--Dust Jacket, Book Cover, Illustrations and Promotional Material 1999 (Box 47)
    - Pay Dirt Original First Draft, with author's corrections 1993 Sep 1, 251 pages; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Pay Dirt Original First Draft, with author's corrections 1993 Sep 1, Electrostatic copy, pages 1-128 (Box 47)
    - Pay Dirt Revised Second Draft, with notes by the editor, Beverly Lewis 1995 Feb 17, 241 pages; 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Pay Dirt Second Draft--Revised 1995 Mar 16, 242 pages; 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Pay Dirt Second Draft--Clean Copy 1995 Mar 16, 242 pages; 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Pay Dirt incorporating all editor's and author's revisions 1995 Mar 30, 241 pages; 2 folders (Box 48)
    - Pay Dirt--Dust Jacket, Book Cover, and Illustrations 1995 (Box 48)
    - Pay Dirt--Book Tour and Review 1995 (Box 48)
    - A Plain Brown Rapper--Extraneous Political Notes n.d., autograph (only--no manuscript) (Box 48)
    - Rest In Pieces Original Manuscript, with author's changes and corrections [ca. 1990?], 314 pages; 2 folder (Box 49)
    - Rest in Pieces First Draft, Clean Copy 1991 Mar 11, 314 pages, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Rest in Pieces Edit Copy by Beverly Lewis, with author's changes and corrections 1991 Mar 11, 275 pages; 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Rest in Pieces with author's changes and corrections 1991 Dec 30, 268 pages; 1 of 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Rest in Pieces, with author's changes and corrections 1991 Dec 30, 268 pages; 1 of 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Rest in Pieces Bantam Copy Edit [1992], Setting Copy, 287 pages; 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Rest in Pieces Page Proofs 1992 (Box 50)
    - Rest in Pieces Uncorrected Proofs Hardcover Publication 1992 Aug 17, 2 copies in 2 folders (Box 50)
    - Rest in Pieces with author's changes and corrections, incomplete n.d., pages 1-85, and 148-195 (Box 50)
    - Rest in Pieces--Dust Jackets and Illustrations 1992 (Box 50)
    - Rest in Pieces--Reviews 1992 (Box 50)
    - Riding Shotgun Original Draft with author's corrections and additions [ca. 1994], 3 folders (Box 51)
    - Riding Shotgun Original Draft, with notes [ca. 1994], Electrostatic copy, pages 1-46, and 52-567, with pages 224-567 apparently mis-numbered; 4 folders (Box 51)
    - Riding Shotgun Original Draft--Part I [ca. 1994], Electrostatic copy (Box 52)
    - Riding Shotgun Original Draft--Rejected pages [ca. 1994] (Box 52)
    - Riding Shotgun Revised Original Draft, with author's changes and corrections 1994 Jul 25, 512 pages; 4 folders (Box 52)
    - Riding Shotgun First Draft--Edit 1994 Jul 25, 516 pages; 4 folders (Box 53)
    - Riding Shotgun Final Proof--Edit 1995 Feb 8, 497 pages; 3 folders (Box 53)
    - Riding Shotgun Setting Copy 1995 Mar-Apr, 3 folders (Box 54)
    - Riding Shotgun n.d., 3 folders (Box 54)
    - Riding Shotgun--Book Tour and Reviews 1996 (Box 54)
    - Riding Shotgun--Correspondence 1994 (Box 54)
    - Riding Shotgun--Dust Jacket and Book Cover 1995 (Box 55)
    - Riding Shotgun--Notes and Research ca. 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box 55)
    - Rita Will First Draft, with author's changes and corrections 1996, 575 pages; 4 folders (Box 55)
    - Rita Will First Draft, with author's changes and corrections 1996, Electrostatic copy, pages 1-307, and 425-568; 1 of 3 folders (Box 55)
    - Rita Will First Draft, with author's changes and corrections 1996, Electrostatic copy, pages 1-307, and 425-568; 2 of 3 folders (Box 56)
    - Rita Will Clean Copy [1996 Oct?], 617 pages; 4 folders (Box 56)
    - Rita Will with a few corrections [1996 Oct 13], 617 pages; 4 folders (Box 57)
    - Rita Will Addenda Pages [1996 Oct 13] (Box 57)
    - Rita Will Addenda Pages, with author's changes and corrections ca. 1997 May 5 (Box 57)
    - Rita Will Addenda Pages, with author's changes and corrections 1997 May 5 (Box 57)
    - Rita Will Addenda Pages 1997 May (Box 58)
    - Rita Will Drafts of Autobiography Introduction and Hunt Insert 1997 May 14 and 30 (Box 58)
    - Rita Will Setting Copy 1997 May, 726 pages; 5 folders (Box 58)
    - Rita Will Page Proofs--Second Pass 1997 Jul 11, 3 folders (Box 59)
    - Rita Will--Book Cover and Publicity [1997] (Box 59)
    - Rita Will--Book Tour 1997 (Box 59)
    - Rita Will--Correspondence 1997-1998, 3 folders (Box 59)
    - Rita Will--Insert Pages n.d. (Box 59)
    - Rita Will--Reviews 1997 and 1999 (Box 60)
    - Rubyfruit Jungle--Book Tour and Book Cover 1977 (Box 60)
    - Rubyfruit Jungle--Contract and Correspondence 1973-1987 (Box 60)
    - Rubyfruit Jungle--Reviews and Publicity 1975-1977 (Box 60)
    - Six of One Original Autograph Manuscript Dialogue and Notes [ante 1978], 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Six of One Original Draft Typescript [ante 1978], 3 folders (Box 60)
    - Six of One--Book Covers n.d. (Box 60)
    - Six of One--Book Tour ca. 1978 (Box 60)
    - Six of One--Notes n.d. (Box 60)
    - Six of One--Reviews and Publicity 1978-1979 (Box 60)
    - Sneak Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers Original Copy 1997 Jan (Box 61)
    - Sneak Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers First Draft with First Corrections in green ink [ca. 1997 Jan] (Box 61)
    - Sneaky Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers with penciled page numbers and corrections in red ink [ca. 1997 Jan] (Box 61)
    - Sneak Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers 1997 Jan 10 (Box 61)
    - Sneaky Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers 1998 Jan 19 (Box 61)
    - Sneaky Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers ca. 1998 Mar (Box 61)
    - Sneaky Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers, with author's changes and corrections, plus two autograph pages n.d. (Box 61)
    - Sneaky Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers Clean Copy n.d. (Box 61)
    - Sneaky Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers Setting Copy [ca. 1998 Dec ?] (Box 61)
    - Sneaky Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers Page Proofs 1999 Jan 5 (Box 61)
    - Sneaky Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers--Correspondence 1996 and 1998 (Box 61)
    - Sneaky Pie's Cookbook for Mystery Lovers--Illustrations and Reviews 1998-1999 (Box 61)
    - Southern Discomfort First Draft ca. 1981, 351 pages; 2 of 3 folders (Box 61)
    - Southern Discomfort First Draft ca. 1981, 351 pages; 1 of 3 folders (Box 62)
    - Southern Discomfort, with author's changes and corrections 1981 Jun 4, 371 pages, 3 folders (Box 62)
    - Southern Discomfort--Notes, Book Cover, and Review ca. 1982 and n.d. (Box 62)
    - Starting from Scratch--Reviews 1998 (Box 62)
    - Sudden Death--Dust Jacket and Book Cover ca. 1983-1984 (Box 62)
    - [Tale] of the Tip-Off First Draft with author's corrections and changes [ca. 2001 Feb], 381 pages; 3 folders (Box 62)
    - [Tale] of the Tip-Off First Draft with author's corrections and changes 2001 Feb 6, 462 pages; 1 of 3 folders (Box 62)
    - [Tale] of the Tip-Off First Draft with author's corrections and changes 2001 Feb 6, 462 pages; 2 of 3 folders (Box 63)
    - Venus Envy Original Draft, with author's changes and corrections [1992 Jun ?], pages 1-148 (Box 63)
    - Venus Envy Computer Version of Original Draft, incorporating changes by author 1992 Jun 3, pages 1-148 (Box 63)
    - Venus Envy Original Draft, with author's changes and corrections 1992 Jun 3, pages 149-393; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Venus Envy Clean Copy 1992 Jun 15, 448 pages; 1 of 3 folders (Box 63)
    - Venus Envy Clean Copy 1992 Jun 15, 448 pages; 2 of 3 folders (Box 64)
    - Venus Envy Edit Copy 1992 Aug 3, 447 pages; 3 folders (Box 64)
    - Venus Envy Drafts of Miscellaneous Sections [1992 Aug 3?], 2 folders (Box 64)
    - Venus Envy Setting Copy 1992 Nov 14, 458 pages; 3 folders (Box 65)
    - Venus Envy--Book Tour 1993 (Box 65)
    - Venus Envy--Correspondence 1993 (Box 65)
    - Venus Envy--Notes 1992, n.d. (Box 65)
    - Venus Envy--Proposal ca. 1991 (Box 65)
    - Venus Envy--Reviews 1993 (Box 65)
    - Wish You Were Here First Draft [1989], 300 pages; 1 of 2 folders (Box 65)
    - Wish You Were Here First Draft [1989], 300 pages, 2 of 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Wish You Were Here Original Second Draft, with author's changes and corrections [1989 Jul 24], 300 pages; 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Wish You Were Here Edited Copy Second Draft Master File [ca. 1989 Aug?], 314 pages; 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Wish You Were Here Edited Copy Second Draft Master File, with chapters divided by pink and yellow sheets [ca. 1989 Aug?], 314 pages; 1 of 2 folders (Box 66)
    - Wish You Were Here Edited Copy Second Draft Master File, with chapters divided by pinkand yellow sheets [ca. 1989 Aug?], 314 pages; 1 of 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Wish You Were Here Working Copy Second Draft, edited for Third Draft, with Rita Mae Brown's rewrites of chapters 1-2, Beverly Lewis copy [ca. 1989], 314 pages; 1 of 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Wish You Were Here Working Copy Second Draft, edited for Third Draft, with Rita Mae Brown's rewrites of chapters 1-2, American Artists copy [ca. 1989], 314 pages; 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Wish You Were Here Clean Copy [1990 Jan 26], 321 pages; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Wish You Were Here Setting Copy 1990 Dec, 321 pages; 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Wish You Were Here Uncorrected Proofs Hardcover publication 1990 Nov 5, 2 copies in 2 folders (Box 68)
    - Wish You Were Here--Book Tour and Reviews 1990 and 1993 (Box 68)
    - Wish You Were Here--Correspondence 1989-1990 (Box 68)
    - Wish You Were Here--Dust Jacket and Book Cover 1990 (Box 68)
    - Wish You Were Here--Illustrations 1990-1991 (Box 68)
  - Screenplays and Teleplays arranged by Title
    - "The Alice Marble Story" Outline on Notecards 1986, 2 folders (Box 69)
    - "The Alice Marble Story" [Original Draft?] with author's changes and corrections ca. 1986 Feb, 106 pages (Box 69)
    - "The Alice Marble Story" [First Draft?] with author's changes and corrections ca. 1986 Feb?, 126 pages (Box 69)
    - "The Alice Marble Story" Clean Copy ca. 1986 Feb?, 107 pages (Box 69)
    - "The Alice Marble Story" with author's changes and corrections 1986 Mar 12, 107 pages (Box 69)
    - "The Alice Marble Story" with author's changes and corrections 1986 Mar, 116 pages (Box 69)
    - "The Alice Marble Story" 1986 Mar 27, 111 pages; 2 copies in 2 folders (Box 69)
    - "The Alice Marble Story"--Correspondence and Notes 1986-1987 (Box 70)
    - "Blood Sports" with author's changes and corrections 1995, 5 drafts (Box 70)
    - "Death and Taxes" Typescripts 1992-1993 (Box 70)
    - "Death and Taxes" Proposal 1993 (Box 70)
    - "Don't Open the Door" n.d. (Box 70)
    - "A Family Again" Outline, Character List, and Alvin Cooperman's Notes 1993 Dec 2-6 (Box 70)
    - "A Family Again" Partial Typescript, including Notes 1993 Dec 6 (Box 70)
    - "A Family Again" Original First Draft 1994 Jan 14, 118 pages (Box 70)
    - "A Family Again" Draft One--Edited 1994 Jan 24, 126 pages (Box 70)
    - "A Family Again" Draft One--Final (incomplete) 1994 Jan 28 (Box 71)
    - "A Family Again" First Draft Edit with changes and corrections [1994 Jan], 128 pages (Box 71)
    - "A Family Again" Draft One Revised, with Notes, dated November 17, 1993 1994 Mar 18, 122 pages, Electrostatic copy (Box 71)
    - "A Family Again' First Draft Edited Revised 1994 Mar 20, 122 pages (Box 71)
    - "A Family Again" First Draft--First Set of Revisions 1994 Mar 21, 105 pages (Box 71)
    - "A Family Again" Revised First Draft--Final Edit 1994 Mar 21, 101 pages; 2 copies (Box 71)
    - "A Family Again" Additional Comments 1994 Mar 21 and 31, 113 pages (Box 71)
    - "A Family Again" Second Set of Revisions 1994 Sep 6, 112 pages (Box 72)
    - "A Family Again" Third Draft 1994 Sep 6, 112 pages (Box 72)
    - "A Family Again"--Correspondence and Notes 1993 Sep-Dec (Box 72)
    - "The Girls of Summer" written by Kenneth F. Sylk, with correspondence between Rita Mae Brown and Mark Schelmerdine 1987 (Box 72)
    - "The Girls of Summers" Early Draft and Notes [1988] Feb, 216 pages; 2 folders (Box 72)
    - "The Girls of Summer" Scene by Scene Breakdown [ca. 1988 Mar] (Box 72)
    - "The Girls of Summer" Scene by Scene Breakdown, and Character Sketches, including Correspondence 1988 Mar 3 (Box 72)
    - "The Girls of Summer" Scene by Scene Breakdown with Changes and Corrections [1988 Mar 3] (Box 72)
    - "The Girls of Summer" 1988 Sep 18, 146 pages (Box 72)
    - "The Girls of Summer" First Draft and Script Delivery Notice 1988 Sep 22, 147 pages (Box 73)
    - "The Girls of Summer" First Draft by Ruth Charny [ca. 1988 Sep], 153 pages (Box 73)
    - "The Girls of Summer" with notes from Ruth Charny and Mark Shelmerdine 1988 Oct 14, 228 pages, 2 folders (Box 73)
    - "The Girls of Summer" Second Draft--1st Cut, with changes and corrections [ca. 1988], 153 pages (Box 73)
    - "The Girls of Summer" Second Draft with changes and corrections 1989 Jan 12, 109 pages (Box 73)
    - "The Girl of Summer" Second Draft 1989 Jan 12, Electrostatic Copy, 140 pages (Box 74)
    - "The Girls of Summer" Second Draft, including notes by Ruth Charny [ca. 1989 Jan], 143 pages (Box 74)
    - "The Girls of Summer", with three articles about Girls Professional Baseball League 1989 Mar 29, 124 pages (Box 74)
    - "The Girls of Summer" Third Draft 1989 Mar 30, 121 pages; 2 copies in 2 folders (Box 74)
    - "The Girls of Summer" Third Draft, with Notes by Ruth Charny 1989 Mar 30, 121 pages (Box 74)
    - "The Girls of Summer" Third Draft 1989 Apr 7, 121 pages (Box 75)
    - "The Girls of Summer" Third Draft 1989 Apr 10, 116 pages (Box 75)
    - "The Girls of Summer" Third Draft, 1st Set Revisions 1989 Jun 11, 116 pages (Box 75)
    - "The Girls of Summer' 1989 Jun, 115 pages (Box 75)
    - "The Girls of Summer" 1989 Jun 11, Electrostatic Copy, 120 pages (Box 75)
    - "The Girls of Summer" n.d., 228 pages (Box 75)
    - "The Girls of Summer" incomplete n.d., 78 pages (Box 75)
    - "The Girls of Summer" with changes and corrections n.d., 165 pages (Box 75)
    - "The Girls of Summer" with changes and corrections n.d., 145 pages (Box 75)
    - "Gluttony/The Seven Deadly Sins" 1992 Jun-Nov (Box 76)
    - "Gluttony/The Seven Deadly Sins" First Draft and Edits 1992 Dec-1993 Jan (Box 76)
    - "Gluttony/The Seven Deadly Sins" Originals and Copies 1993 Jan 18 and 21 (Box 76)
    - "Gluttony/The Seven Deadly Sins" Revised First Draft 1993 Jan 22 and 25 (Box 76)
    - "Gluttony/The Seven Deadly Sins" Second Revision--Final 1993 Feb 18 (Box 76)
    - "The Seven Deadly Sins" including "Gluttony" by Rita Mae Brown 1995 Apr 3 (Box 76)
    - "Gluttony/The Seven Deadly Sins"--Correspondence and Research 1992-1993 (Box 77)
    - Graced Land: The Novel by Laura Kalpakian ca. 1991, Bound Typescript Copy (Box 77)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis") Original Autograph Manuscript of the Teleply by Rita Mae Brown 1991 Nov 14, 162 pages (Box 77)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis") Scene by Scene Breakdowns 1991 and n.d. (Box 77)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis") Proof Copy--No Act One 1992 Jan 10, pages 26-103 (Box 77)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis"), with changes and corrections 1992 Jan, 104 pages (Box 77)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Women Who Loved Elvis") Proof Copy 1992 Jan 13, 117 pages (Box 78)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis") First Draft 1992 Jan 14, 115 pages (Box 78)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis") First Draft Edit 1992 Mar 30, 115 pages (Box 78)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis" Second Draft 1992 Apr 6, 104 pages (Box 78)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis") Revised Second Draft (Original) 1992 Apr 30, 104 pages (Box 78)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis") Revised Second Draft (Copy) 1992 Apr 30, 104 pages (Box 78)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis") Revised Second Draft (Copy)s 1992 Apr 30, 104 pages (Box 78)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis") Revised Second Draft Final--Scriptor Edit Proof 1992 Apr 30, 98 pages (Box 78)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis") Revised Second Draft with Crew List dated May 13, 1992 1992 Apr 30, 98 pages (Box 78)
    - "Graceland' (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis') Revised Second Draft 1992 [May 1], 98 pages (Box 79)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as the "The Woman Who Loved Elvis") Teleplay Revised Draft 1992 May 25-Jun 17, 96 pages; 2 copies in 2 folders (Box 79)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis")--Correspondence 1991-1992 (Box 79)
    - "Graceland" (later produced as "The Woman Who Loved Elvis")--Notes 1991, 2 folders (Box 79)
    - "The Headless Horseman" Proposal 1993 (Box 79)
    - "Home, Sweet Home" Original First Draft and Notes [1989], 112 pages (Box 79)
    - "Home, Sweet Home' Original First Draft, [1989], Electrostatic Copy, 112 pages (Box 79)
    - "Home, Sweet Home" Typescript Draft [1989], 99 pages (Box 79)
    - "Home, Sweet Home", Act One missing 1990 May 23, pages 22-118 (Box 80)
    - "Home, Sweet Home" Original Revision 1990 Jul 9, 76 pages (Box 80)
    - "Home, Sweet Home" Original Revision--Reprinted 1990 Jul 10, 102 pages (Box 80)
    - "Home, Sweet Home" 1990 Jul 17, 119 pages (Box 80)
    - "Home, Sweet Home" Second Draft 1990 Sep 6, 101 pages (Box 80)
    - "Home, Sweet Home" Original Second Draft--Revised 1990 Sep 6, 119 pages (Box 80)
    - "Home, Sweet Home" Mid-Revision 1990 Sep 6, 104 pages (Box 80)
    - "Home, Sweet Home" Second Draft, Final Revision with Original Ending 1990 Sep [6], 117 pages (Box 80)
    - "Home, Sweet Home" Final Revision Clean Copy 1990 Sep 6, 108 pages (Box 81)
    - "Home, Sweet Home" with changes and corrections n.d., 113 pages (Box 81)
    - "Home, Sweet Home"--Correspondence, Notes, and Contracts 1989-1990 (Box 81)
    - "I Love Liberty" 1982 Feb (Box 81)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" Screenplay by Irving Ravetch and Harriet Frank, Jr. 1957 Aug 26, Electrostatic Copy (Box 81)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" Part One Outline and Part Two Synopis 1983 Dec 1 (Box 81)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" [Original First Draft?] [1984?], 90 pages (Box 81)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" [Original First Draft--Clean Copy?] [1984?], 93 pages (Box 81)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" Part One, First Draft 1984 Jan 10, Electrostatic Copy. 127 pages (Box 82)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" Part One, with changes and corrections [1984], Electrostatic Copy, 104 pages (Box 82)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" Part One, with changes and corrections [1984], 115 pages (Box 82)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" First Draft with changes and corrections 1984 Feb 16, 120 pages (Box 82)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" Part Two, First Draft, with notes re script by Rita Mae Brown 1984 Sep 13, 104 pages (Box 82)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" Part One, Second Draft [1984 May 11], 102 pages (Box 82)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" Part One, Second Draft 1984 May 11, Electrostatic copy; 102 pages (Box 82)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" Shooting Script, Parts One and Two 1985 Mar-Apr, 205 pages; 1 of 2 folders (Box 82)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" Shooting Script, Parts One and Two 1985 Mar-Apr, 205 pages; 2 of 2 folders (Box 83)
    - "The Long Hot Summer" Shooting Script, Parts One and Two 1985 Mar-Apr, 205 pages; 2 folders (Box 83)
    - "The Long Hot Summer'--Correspondence and Viewer's Guide 1985-1986 (Box 83)
    - "The Long Hot Summer"--Notecards n.d., 2 folders (Box 83)
    - "Mary Pickford: A Life on Film" Original Draft, Autograph Manuscript and Typescripts 1996 Sep 23 (Box 83)
    - "Mary Pickford: A Life on Film" Original Draft, Two Typescript Copies 1996 Sep 23 (Box 83)
    - "Mary Pickford: A Life on Film" with changes and corrections 1996 Oct and Nov 3, 42 pages (Box 83)
    - "Mary Pickford: A Life on Film" 1996 Nov 5, 41 pages (Box 83)
    - "Mary Pickford: A Life on Film"--Research Material, including correspondence about the film 1996-1998 (Box 84)
    - "Mary Pickford: A Life on Film"--Research Material--Articles 1966-1989, n.d. (Box 84)
    - "The Mists of Avalon" Treatment [1986?] (Box 84)
    - "The Mists of Avalon" Scene by Scene Breakdowns, with changes and corrections [1986], one copy numbered 1-299, 3 copies (Box 85)
    - "The Mists of Avalon" Scene by Scene Breakdowns 1986 Nov 27 (Box 84)
    - "The Mists of Avalon" Prologue and Notes 1986 (Box 84)
    - "The Mists of Avalon" Original Draft, with changes and corrections 1987 Jan, 219 pages (Box 84)
    - "The Mists of Avalon" First Draft, with changes and corrections 1987 Jan, 236 pages; 2 folders (Box 84)
    - "The Mists of Avalon" First Draft, Clean Copy [1987 Jan], 246 pages; 2 folders (Box 85)
    - "Mists of Avalon" First Draft--Revised ca. 1987 Feb, 246 pages; 3 folders (Box 85)
    - "The Mists of Avalon" Second Draft, with changes and corrections 1987 Mar 21, 257 pages; 2 folders (Box 85)
    - "The Mists of Avalon" Second Draft, Clean Copy 1987 Mar 22, 257 pages; 2 folders (Box 86)
    - "The Mists of Avalon" Second Draft, Clean Copy 1987 Mar 22, 257 pages; 2 folders (Box 86)
    - "The Mists of Avalon" Second Draft, Clean Copy 1987 Mar 22, 257 pages; 2 folders (Box 86)
    - "The Mists of Avalon"--Contract and Correspondence 1986-1987 (Box 86)
    - "The Mists of Avalon"--Notes and Research 1986-1987 (Box 86)
    - "My Two Loves' Screenplay by Reginald Rose, with Notes 1984 Oct 25, 111 pages (Box 87)
      re the Script by Rita Mae Brown, dated January 1985
    - "My Two Loves" Screenplay by Reginald Rose and Rita Mae Brown, with changes and corrections 1985 Feb 23, 116 pages (Box 87)
    - "My Two Loves" Screenplay by Reginald Rose and Rita Mae Brown, with changes and corrections, with a memorandum from Alvin Cooperman 1985 Apr 8, Electrostatic Copy, 107 pages (Box 87)
    - "My Two Loves" Screenplay by Reginald Rose and Rita Mae Brown 1985 May 30, 116 pages (Box 87)
    - "My Two Loves" Screenplay by Reginald Rose and Rita Mae Brown 1985 May 30, 120 pages (Box 87)
    - "My Two Loves" Screenplay by Reginald Rose and Rita Mae Brown 1985 Jul 16, Electrostatic copy; 103 pages (Box 87)
    - "My Two Loves" Screenplay by Reginald Rose and Rita Mae Brown 1985 Aug 15, Electrostatic Copy, 103 pages; 2 copies in 2 folders (Box 87)
    - "My Two Loves" Screenplay by Reginald Rose and Rita Mae Brown 1986 Jan 3, Electrostatic Copy, 108 pages (Box 88)
    - "My Two Loves" Screenplay by Reginald Rose and Rita Mae Brown 1986 Jan 23, Electrostatic Copy, 109 pages (Box 88)
    - "My Two Loves" Screenplay by Reginald Rose and Rita Mae Brown, with revisions 1986 Feb 22, 109 pages (Box 88)
    - "Nat Turner Story" Original Draft and Edited Drafts 1993 Apr 10-13, 3 copies (Box 88)
    - "Nat Turner Story" Revised Drafts and Final Draft 1993 Apr-Jun, 4 copies (Box 88)
    - "Nat Turner Story"--Contacts, Correspondence, Notes, and Outline 1992 Dec-1993 Mar (Box 88)
    - "Passing Through" Script Outlines 1992 Dec-1993 Mar, 2 folders (Box 88)
    - "Passing Through" Script Outlines [1992 Aug-Sep ?], 2 folders (Box 89)
    - "Passing Through" Script Outlines--"Final," one with changes and corrections and clean copy 1992 Sep 15, 2 copies (Box 89)
    - "Passing Through" Script Outline incorporating Stu Samuel's Notes 1992 Dec 15 (Box 89)